Abd Alkafi Albrejawi

- **Software engineer** (Mobile App Developer - iOS & Android || Expert FlutterDeveloper || WordPress designer) with +3 years on Software development with a focus on frontend side ,

Published 2 Flutter applications on the Google & Play Store.

I currently work at Oryx Sky as an IT support specialist, where I manage student and teacher accounts for various schools we collaborate with, in addition to performing data entry tasks. - Previously worked within the Syrian Arab Red Crescent, contributing to several teams. Contact us for more info.

Dubai , UAE , (+971) 0589231134

-https://kafibrejawi.github.io/protofolio

-https://www.linkedin.com/in

/Abd-AlKafi/

-https://github.com/kafiBrejawi/

-Kafi.brejawi@gmail.com

EXPERIENCE

Oryx Sky Company — Program Support

01/03/ 2024 - Current \ Dubai

Freelancer — Website Designer Using WordPress

01/01/2020 - Current

Netwitcher Company — *ASP .NET MVC Developer*

01/10/2023 - 05/09/2024

 It is a company specializing in the field of electronic marketing, development and applications in addition to creating web pages andmanaging content.

Syrian Arab Red Crescent — Mobile Application Programming

01/01/2020 - 01/06/2023

- Implemented a comprehensive paramedic registration system, streamlining shift management for over 100 ambulance personnel across the city's branches and enhancing operational efficiency by eliminating scheduling errors in real-time..
- Data entry and periodic data filtering.

Syriatel Company — Customer Service Representative

01/02/2023 - 01/06/2023

- Managed high-volume customer inquiries through phone and email channels.
- Identified customer needs through active listening techniques to initiate referrals to colleagues.

Syrian Computer Society — Training C++ Language for Adolescents and Children

03/04/2022 - 31/05/2022

EDUCATION

AL Baath University , Homs /Syria — Bachelor's degree in Information Engineering, Software Engineering Department

SKILLS

Ui/Ux designer on Figma | Adobe premiere | Ability to work in a team and autonomously | Ability to intervene and manage the group

MVC | Git-hub | Html-Css

|C++| #C | dart

VOLUNTEERING

Syrian Arab Red Crescent – Volunteer in the Human Resources Section

18/06/2023 - 01/01/2024

- Data Entry and Record-keeping.
- Document Management and Submission:
- Submit original documents to the appropriate document management system or department
- Application Form Processing and Review:
- Assist New Volunteers in filling out. Application forms accurately and completely.
- · Review New Volunteers order details.

Syrian Arab Red Crescent – Paramedic

18/12/2018 - 09/03/2023

- Team leader from 2019 to 2022.
- Coordinator in the Operations Centre until 2022.

LANGUAGES

Mother tongue(s): Arabic

TOP PROJECTS

1 - Monawbaty App

Link: https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.shk.monawpaty

- A software application developed in 2021 for the first aid system in the Syrian Arab Red Crescent organization.
- Developed a cross platform application using flutter framework.
- Implemented user authentication and authorization using firebase authentication.
- Utilized cubit package for state management.
- Integrated Google Maps Api for Location-based event planning.

2- Atlas App

<u>Link:</u> https://www.linkedin.com/company/atlas-elevators-factory/

- It is an application of an elevator company located in the UAE
- Developed a cross platform application using flutter framework.
- Utilized cubit package for state management.
- Automate the working method of the maintenance worker.
- Many features have been used and are important for digital expectation.

3- Dietitian-Souad

Link: https://souad-dietitian.viyana-tech.com/

- o WordPress website with responsive UI.
- It is a site created for a nutritionist with the aim of offering her range of services in addition to facilitate the process of communicating with her patients in ways selected and included in the site.

4- zetainspection.com

Link: https://zetainspection.com/

• WordPress website with responsive UI.